http://www.cravenpotholeclub.org/index.php/16-about-us/55-data-protection-policy

Toggle Navigation
HomeAbout UsHow To JoinThe CottagesActivitiesA Short History of the CPCPublicationsSurveysApplication Form & RulesCPC RecordLearn To CaveConservationAbout Gaping GillGaping Gill Winch MeetGetting to Gaping GillVisit Gaping GillVisitors FAQVisiting Cavers FAQA Brief History of ExplorationGaping Gill - Further ReadingGaping Gill - BibliographyPhoto GalleryExplorationMarilynLancashire Hotpot100 Years of Caving1900 to 19091910 to 19191920 to 19291930 to 19391940 to 19491950 to 19591960 to 19691970 to 19791980 - 19891990 - 1999CreditsCottage BookingsLinksContact UsMembers
Craven Pothole Club Ltd. (CPC)General Data Protection Regulation - Privacy Policy
Information we collect about you
The CPC collects data from its members in an online database on the cravenpotholeclub.org website. This data may have been entered into the membership application form or voluntarily by you into the membership database.
How we store your information
The CPC takes all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of the site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
How we use your information
The CPC will only use personal information to provide you with services relating to the CPC, primarily distribution of the club magazine “The Record” and other club related matters.Your data is stored securely on UK based servers.For insurance purposes some of your data (BCA number, name, address, year of birth, gender) is shared with the British Caving Association (BCA). If you consent to share your email address with the BCA to aid in their processes please give the appropriate consent.As CPC shareholders your data is shared with the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA).Personal information will not be passed to other third parties.
Children
Children aged 16 or under wishing to provide personal details to the CPC should get their parent/guardian's permission to do so.
Your rights
All your personal data held by us is available to view/amend on our website. You will have been notified of your username and password on joining the organisation. You will have been asked for your consent/non-consent on the membership form to share.    1. (Personal Data) - share your personal data with other members    2. (Historic Data) - share historic data (name, date of joining, date of leaving) for the “Rogues Gallery”    3. (BCA Data) – share your gender*/email address with the BCA    4. add your name/email address to the email distribution listYour consent for sharing Personal/Historic/BCA Data may be changed at any time by accessing your personal data on the website and giving/withdrawing your consents. Withdrawing consent for your Personal Data will make that data only accessible by the Officers of the club for the legitimate purposes described above. Every email from the distribution list contains a link to allow members to unsubscribe from it.On leaving the club your personal data will be deleted at the end of the financial year of your departure. If you have consented, your historic data will be retained.If you think we have misused your personal data you may complain to the Information Commissioner's Office (ico.org.uk)
Cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site.Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We may collect information about your computer, including (where available) your IP address, operating system and browser type. The Club makes no use of this information.You may refuse to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you visit the site.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.
* - added gender - 4/05/2018
You are here:
Meets ListView Full Calendar12 Dec 2020;
10:00AM -
Marble Steps Pot
13 Dec 2020;
10:00AM -
Caves of Ribblehead
27 Dec 2020;
10:00AM -
Swinsto Hole
09 Jan 2021;
10:00AM -
Pool Sink
10 Jan 2021;
10:00AM -
Scoska Cave
Tweets by @cravenpothole
